We All Scream for Ice Cream is a horror, tv movie film directed by Tom Holland.
Years ago, they pulled a disastrous childhood prank on the neighborhood ice cream delivery man that got him killed, but now as they've become adults
with families of their own, the last thing anyone expected was for that man to come back in the form of a vengeful, bloodthirsty spirit.
Buster, played by William Forsythe.
Layne, played by Lee Tergesen.
Kent, played by Brent Sheppard.
Kenny, played by Maxwell Neck.
Papa Joe, played by Tim Henry.
Darlene, played by Laura Drummond.
"We All Scream for Ice Cream" is an episode of the series
Masters of Horror directed by Tom Holland.
It was based on the story "You Scream, I Scream, We All Scream for Ice Cream" by John Farris;
the title evoking the song "I Scream, You Scream, We All Scream for Ice Cream".
The tone is dark.